Rita Braunschweig

+45 71818891 | ritabb04.05@gmail.com | Sønderborg, Denmark

ABOUT ME

I am a first-year Software Engineering student passionate about taking on challenges and contributing to meaningful projects. My motivation and dedication push me to continuously learn. I bring a proactive and openminded approach to every task, enabling me to quickly adapt and learn. I value teamwork, and my patient nature allows me to collaborate effectively in group settings. I am committed to applying my skills, while also learning from new experiences, to contribute positively to any project.

SKILLS

- C#
- Visual Studio Code
- Microsoft Office

- Jira
- GitHub
- xUnit

Avalonia UI

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Board member in IDA STEM Students.
- Grade 12 in Object-Oriented Programming.
- Honour student in high school.

EXPERIENCE

Object-Oriented Programming Project – Team Leader

06/09/2023 - 17/12/2023

- Programming language: C#
- Developed EcoCity, a console-based sustainable city builder game, by designing mechanics for constructing and demolishing buildings in different areas of the city, managing day cycles, finances, population, pollution, and population happiness, resulting in an engaging and educational experience for users.

Object-Oriented Programming Project – Scrum Master

06/02/2024 - 03/06/2024

- Programming language: C#
- Developed a heating optimization application for Danfoss, incorporating four production units. The
 application allows the user to optimize heating production based on net costs, CO2 emissions, or both. Users
 can visualize the results through a graph or a csv file, providing clear insights for efficient heating
 management.

EDUCATION

University of Southern Denmark

Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering

2023 - current

• Entered with an average of an equivalent to a grade 10 in the Danish grading system.